[Music]
production bill of material is a key
component in the manufacturing in this
release we enhance usability to make
sure it's easier for you to maintain the
list of components needed to produce
product but it's easier to see in the
demo and let's start with the production
bill of material the first thing you
probably notice is document attachment
where you can add additional information
like drawings or specifications or other
m materials needed there's also an
active version that you can access via
the assist edit
button how does this version differ from
the main bill of material the new
version comparison Matrix includes all
information about the main bill of
material as well as available versions
different option levels can be adjusted
to determine how subassemblies are
displayed whether as entire
subassemblies or their individual
components let's review our second
version navigate to the version list
where the starting date and the status
are
displayed proceed with the edits as
usual or use the select items action to
select multiple items at
once ensure quantities are
updated consider using the edit and
Excel functionality for a large bill of
materials close the version
starting from this release a
confirmation dialogue appears if the
status is not
certified certify the version and
attempt to close the page
again let's see where this production
bill of material is
used navigate to the
item they actions related to assembly
and the production bill of materials
you can open the main bill of material
and navigate to the active version or
jump directly to the certified version
based on the current
date thank you for watching you can
learn more about this capability in the
release note also remember to watch
other videos about enhancement on
manufacturing area you can find links in
the description